yardhouse.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Yard House Restaurant

Our Privacy Notice (the “Notice”) describes the information we collect from and about you during your visit to our online interfaces, (including websites, mobile applications, social media or other digital channels), or via your in-restaurant interactions, and through your interaction with in-restaurant devices owned or controlled by us (collectively, the “Sites”). It also describes how we use information about you, and with whom we share it. This Notice applies only to those Darden interfaces that link directly to this Notice. 

The terms “we,” “our,” and “us” in this Notice refer to Darden and its family of companies. It's important to know that our websites may contain links to third party sites not controlled by Darden or covered by this Notice. We recommend that you check the privacy statements of other sites you visit before providing any personal information. 

##  Personal Information We Collect 

We collect Personal Information ("PI") about you from the information you provide to us when you visit our Site. The information we collect will depend on the Site you visit. This information includes: 

  * Name;
  * Address;
  * Phone numbers (including mobile);
  * Email address;
  * Date of birth;
  * Payment information such as payment card details, financial account information and billing address;
  * Names, postal addresses, e-mail addresses and telephone numbers of others to whom you ask us to send information;
  * Username and password to access Darden products and services online;
  * Online order and reservation history;
  * Internet Protocol (IP) Address and/or domain;
  * Geo-location of your computer or mobile device;
  * Mobile carrier and/or Internet Service Provider;
  * Other personal information you may provide to us.

We use personal information collected online for various functions, which may include: 

  * Create and manage your account;
  * Offer and provide products and services to you;
  * Process and collect payments for goods and services;
  * Communicate about, and administer your participation in, special events, programs, rewards, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, and other offers or promotions;
  * Send information to others if you ask us to do so;
  * Respond to and communicate with you about your requests, concerns, questions and comments;
  * Operate, evaluate and improve our business
  * Perform data analyses
  * Protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims and other liabilities; and

Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and our policies. For example, we may use the information you provide when you complete an online order, transaction, or reservation. When you sign up with our eclub, or rewards and provide us with your contact information, we may also use that information to contact you with news and special offers. 

To the extent permitted by applicable law and with your consent where required, we also use information collected through automated means for purposes such as (i) customizing our users’ visits to our Site, (ii) delivering content (including advertising) tailored to our users’ interests and the manner in which our users browse our Site, and (iii) managing our Site and other aspects of our business. To the extent permitted by applicable law, we also may use this information to provide you with ads about our products when you browse this and other websites. 

##  How Personal Information Is Shared 

Unless you ask or authorize us to do so, or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not trade, rent, sell, or share your Personal Information collected from this website or through your use of the Services with non-affiliated third parties. We may share the personal information we collect about you with third parties, such as companies performing services on our behalf to provide the products or services you have requested, to process transactions, complete reservations, enter contests and sweepstakes, engage with you on social platforms, market to you, track rewards, conduct surveys, or facilitate requests to send you communications. 

We may share your personal information within the Darden family of restaurants. The Darden Family currently includes Darden, Olive Garden, LongHorn Steakhouse, Cheddar's Scratch Kitchen, Yard House, The Capital Grille, The Capital Burger, Seasons 52, Bahama Breeze and Eddie V's, as well as our affiliates, and subsidiaries. Members of the Darden family who receive this information from us are not authorized to use or share the information, except as set out in this privacy statement. 

**Third Parties**

In order to serve you, we share your Personal Information with service providers or third parties that perform functions on our behalf. 

We may share your personal information with vendors or third parties who provide services to us, such as fulfilling orders, facilitating reservations, providing data processing and other information technology services, managing promotions, managing any rewards programs, surveys, contests, prize draws and sweepstakes, carrying out research and analysis, and personalizing individual Darden customer experiences. We do not allow these vendors to use this information or to share it for any purpose other than as allowed by law or to provide services on our behalf or on an aggregated basis for statistical, benchmarking, or other analytical services. 

As permitted by law, we also share information collected about you with companies with whom we have formal agreements to conduct analysis, engage in customer research, benchmarking, and to improve our products or services. 

We may, for strategic or other business reasons, decide to sell or transfer all or part of our business. As part of that sale or transfer, we may pass information we have collected and stored, including personal information, to anyone involved in the sale or transfer. 

**Compliance With Laws**

We may disclose your Personal Information and other information to third parties, including governmental authorities, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request, or if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Darden, our customers, or the public as required or permitted by law (especially in emergency situations). 

##  Information collected via Cookies 

We use a variety of technologies, including cookies, to collect information about your online/mobile activity when you visit our Site(s). Cookies are small text files that a website server stores on your computer or device. They’re typically used to remember your account login preferences, monitor website traffic, provide customer support like live chat and help us better customize our site for your individual preferences. 

We may also use Flash® objects (sometimes called "Local Shared Objects") as part of our online authentication to help us recognize your computer when you come back to our site. We do not use Flash objects for any online behavioral advertising purpose. 

You can disable cookies by making the appropriate selection from your browser options to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set. However, if 

you choose to disable or delete cookies, you may limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our site. 

##  Online Behavioral Advertising (OBA) on Third Party Sites 

There are three ways we use OBA on third party websites and mobile apps that are not affiliated with Darden. 

###  Interest‐Based Advertising 

The third parties we contract with may use cookies or other technologies to gather interest-based information to customize the ads you see. This information may be combined and linked with data from other sources. Neither the third parties nor Darden collects any personally information (PI) through these cookies. We may also use aggregate data to display ads or content that may interest you. 

Darden has adopted the use of the **AdChoices Icon** (also known as the Advertising Option Icon) on our interest-based advertising (excluding ads appearing on platforms that do not accept the icon). You can learn more about AdChoices by visiting <https://www.aboutads.info/choices/> to learn more and control whether or not you receive this type of advertising from participating companies. 

###  Device-Based Advertising 

We may also use device information, particularly in mobile advertising, to help deliver our ads and measure ad campaign effectiveness. Darden and the companies we work with may collect some certain information when you visit one of our sites or see our ads. Compiling and comparing this information creates a unique ID for individual devices and can be "matched" to the same information on other sites or mobile applications. Some companies we work with are also able to associate related devices into households based on common characteristics, such as IP addresses. 

###  Device Usage Research 

We may participate in the Adobe Marketing Cloud Device Co-op. This helps us understand how you use our website and apps across your devices so that we can better tailor promotions to you. [Learn more about how Adobe’s program works and manage your preferences.](https://cross-device-privacy.adobe.com/)

##  "Do Not Track" Signals 

We do not respond to Web browser "Do Not Track" signals at this time. To prevent us or third parties from tracking, you can access your browser settings and disable or delete your cookies. 

##  Changing or Updating Your Personal Information 

If you have questions about personal information you provided on a Site, contact [privacy@darden.com](mailto:privacy@darden.com;)

##  Personal Information About Children 

We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information about children under the age of 13 unless the personal information is provided by a parent, legal guardian or authorized adult. Our websites are not intended for children under 13. Visit the Federal Trade Commission website for more information on the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).Darden does not sell the personal information of minors under 16 years of age. 

##  Notice to California Residents 

ACCESS TO SPECIFIC INFORMATION AND DATA PORTABILITY RIGHTS 

You have the right, subject to certain exceptions defined in the California Consumer Protection Act “CCPA” and other applicable laws and regulations, to request that companies disclose certain information to you about their collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. This right of access includes information about: 

  * The categories of personal information we collected about you.
  * The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.
  * Our business or commercial purpose for collecting that personal information.
  * The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information.
  * The categories of personal information that each recipient received.
  * The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.

DELETION REQUEST RIGHTS 

You have the right, subject to certain exceptions defined in the CCPA and other applicable laws and regulations, to request that a company delete any of your personal information that it has collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. 

EXERCISING ACCESS, DATA PORTABILITY, AND DELETION RIGHTS 

To exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by either: 

  * Submitting your request [here](https://privacyportal-cdn.onetrust.com/dsarwebform/ba9aad07-e9b8-4a45-8cfa-96268092be69/a1e900a8-bc5c-437d-908a-11bb6e5d1367.html)
  * Calling 1-800-331-2729

Note if you are viewing this information offline please visit our online privacy or call the number above to complete your request. 

The verifiable consumer request must: 

  * Provide sufficient information that allows us to verify, to a reasonably high degree of certainty, that you are the person about whom we collected personal information. This may include requesting that you provide us with at least two or more pieces of personal information to match against personal information about you that we may or may not maintain and which we have determined to be reliable for the purpose of verification.
  * Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you. Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us. We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request. 

You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. 

DO NOT SELL RIGHTS 

You have the right, subject to certain exceptions defined in the CCPA and other applicable laws and regulations, to request that companies stop selling your personal information and refrain from doing so in the future. You may exercise this right by: 

  * Submitting your request [here](https://privacyportal-cdn.onetrust.com/dsarwebform/ba9aad07-e9b8-4a45-8cfa-96268092be69/c769a400-4e8a-4928-8774-ef5aadd34241.html)
  * Calling 1-800-331-2729

Note if you are viewing this information offline please visit our online privacy or call the number above to complete your request. 

Darden may deny a Do Not Sell Request if it has a good-faith, reasonable, and documented belief that the Request is fraudulent. 

AUTHORIZED AGENT 

Only you, or a person you have designated in writing as your authorized agent, or who is registered with the California Secretary of State to act on your behalf, or to whom you have provided power of attorney pursuant to California Probate Code sections 4000 to 4465, (“Authorized Agent”), may make a verifiable consumer request or do not sell request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request or do not sell request on behalf of your minor child. 

If you wish to have an Authorized Agent make a request on your behalf, they will need to provide us with sufficient written proof that you have designated them as your Authorized Agent and we will still require you to provide sufficient information to allow us to reasonably verify that you are the person about whom we collected personal information. 

NON-DISCRIMINATION 

You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not: 

  * Deny you services.
  * Charge you different prices or rates for services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
  * Provide you a different level or quality of services.
  * Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for services or a different level or quality of services.

However, we may offer you certain financial incentives permitted by the CCPA that can result in different prices, rates, or quality levels. Any CCPA-permitted financial incentive we offer will reasonably relate to your personal information’s value and contain written terms that describe the program’s material aspects. Participation in a financial incentive program requires your prior opt in consent, which you may revoke at any time. 

##  Notice to Nevada Residents 

Nevada residents have the right to submit a verified request directing us not to sell their personal information. If you are a Nevada resident, and would like to submit such a request, please send your request to [privacy@darden.com](mailto:privacy@darden.com;). 

##  Public Forums Available On Our Sites And Social Media 

Public forums are available on our Sites, and they may include text, photographs and videos or other file formats that are accessible to the general public. Unless we tell you otherwise, any information you disclose in these areas may become public information. 

We also provide experiences through social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, YouTube and other similar social sharing sites. Any and all information you share on these Social Media sites may be subject to re-sharing and is visible to any visitor to these sites. Refer to each social media site for their Terms of Use and Privacy Policies. 

##  Changes to this Notice 

This Notice is effective December 16, 2019. We reserve the right to modify this Notice at any time for any reason at our discretion. Any change to this Notice will be posted on our Sites and your continued use of such Site shall be deemed your acceptance of any modified terms. 

### Send via Text

We'll include the restaurant's address, phone number and a link to this page.
